  export const conheciementosGerais = [
    {
      category: "General%20Knowledge",
      type: "multiple",
      difficulty: "easy",
      question: "What%20is%20the%20most%20common%20surname%20Wales%3F",
      correct_answer: "Jones",
      incorrect_answers: ["Williams", "Davies", "Evans"],
    },
    {
      category: "General%20Knowledge",
      type: "multiple",
      difficulty: "easy",
      question:
        "In%20the%20video-game%20franchise%20Kingdom%20Hearts%2C%20the%20main%20protagonist%2C%20carries%20a%20weapon%20with%20what%20shape%3F",
      correct_answer: "Key",
      incorrect_answers: ["Sword", "Pen", "Cellphone"],
    },
    {
      category: "General%20Knowledge",
      type: "multiple",
      difficulty: "easy",
      question:
        "Which%20best%20selling%20toy%20of%201983%20caused%20hysteria%2C%20resulting%20in%20riots%20breaking%20out%20in%20stores%3F",
      correct_answer: "Cabbage%20Patch%20Kids",
      incorrect_answers: [
        "Transformers",
        "Care%20Bears",
        "Rubik%E2%80%99s%20Cube",
      ],
    },
    {
      category: "General%20Knowledge",
      type: "multiple",
      difficulty: "easy",
      question:
        "In%20past%20times%2C%20what%20would%20a%20gentleman%20keep%20in%20his%20fob%20pocket%3F",
      correct_answer: "Watch",
      incorrect_answers: ["Money", "Keys", "Notebook"],
    },
    {
      category: "General%20Knowledge",
      type: "multiple",
      difficulty: "easy",
      question: "Area%2051%20is%20located%20in%20which%20US%20state%3F",
      correct_answer: "Nevada",
      incorrect_answers: ["Arizona", "New%20Mexico", "Utah"],
    },
    {
      category: "General%20Knowledge",
      type: "multiple",
      difficulty: "easy",
      question:
        "What%20is%20the%20largest%20organ%20of%20the%20human%20body%3F",
      correct_answer: "Skin",
      incorrect_answers: ["Heart", "large%20Intestine", "Liver"],
    },
    {
      category: "General%20Knowledge",
      type: "multiple",
      difficulty: "easy",
      question:
        "Which%20sign%20of%20the%20zodiac%20is%20represented%20by%20the%20Crab%3F",
      correct_answer: "Cancer",
      incorrect_answers: ["Libra", "Virgo", "Sagittarius"],
    },
    {
      category: "General%20Knowledge",
      type: "multiple",
      difficulty: "easy",
      question:
        "On%20a%20dartboard%2C%20what%20number%20is%20directly%20opposite%20No.%201%3F",
      correct_answer: "19",
      incorrect_answers: ["20", "12", "15"],
    },
    {
      category: "General%20Knowledge",
      type: "multiple",
      difficulty: "easy",
      question:
        "What%20word%20represents%20the%20letter%20%27T%27%20in%20the%20NATO%20phonetic%20alphabet%3F",
      correct_answer: "Tango",
      incorrect_answers: ["Target", "Taxi", "Turkey"],
    },
    {
      category: "General%20Knowledge",
      type: "multiple",
      difficulty: "easy",
      question: "What%20alcoholic%20drink%20is%20made%20from%20molasses%3F",
      correct_answer: "Rum",
      incorrect_answers: ["Gin", "Vodka", "Whisky"],
    },
    {
      category: "General%20Knowledge",
      type: "multiple",
      difficulty: "easy",
      question:
        "Which%20American%20president%20appears%20on%20a%20one%20dollar%20bill%3F",
      correct_answer: "George%20Washington",
      incorrect_answers: [
        "Thomas%20Jefferson",
        "Abraham%20Lincoln",
        "Benjamin%20Franklin",
      ],
    },
    {
      category: "General%20Knowledge",
      type: "multiple",
      difficulty: "easy",
      question:
        "What%20geometric%20shape%20is%20generally%20used%20for%20stop%20signs%3F",
      correct_answer: "Octagon",
      incorrect_answers: ["Hexagon", "Circle", "Triangle"],
    },
    {
      category: "General%20Knowledge",
      type: "multiple",
      difficulty: "easy",
      question: "What%20is%20%22dabbing%22%3F",
      correct_answer: "A%20dance",
      incorrect_answers: [
        "A%20medical%20procedure",
        "A%20sport",
        "A%20language",
      ],
    },
    {
      category: "General%20Knowledge",
      type: "multiple",
      difficulty: "easy",
      question:
        "Which%20one%20of%20the%20following%20rhythm%20games%20was%20made%20by%20Harmonix%3F",
      correct_answer: "Rock%20Band",
      incorrect_answers: [
        "Meat%20Beat%20Mania",
        "Guitar%20Hero%20Live",
        "Dance%20Dance%20Revolution",
      ],
    },
    {
      category: "General%20Knowledge",
      type: "multiple",
      difficulty: "easy",
      question:
        "Red%20Vines%20is%20a%20brand%20of%20what%20type%20of%20candy%3F",
      correct_answer: "Licorice",
      incorrect_answers: ["Lollipop", "Chocolate", "Bubblegum"],
    },
    {
      category: "General%20Knowledge",
      type: "multiple",
      difficulty: "easy",
      question:
        "What%20is%20the%20nickname%20of%20the%20US%20state%20of%20California%3F",
      correct_answer: "Golden%20State",
      incorrect_answers: [
        "Sunshine%20State",
        "Bay%20State",
        "Treasure%20State",
      ],
    },
    {
      category: "General%20Knowledge",
      type: "multiple",
      difficulty: "easy",
      question:
        "What%20is%20on%20display%20in%20the%20Madame%20Tussaud%27s%20museum%20in%20London%3F",
      correct_answer: "Wax%20sculptures",
      incorrect_answers: [
        "Designer%20clothing",
        "Unreleased%20film%20reels",
        "Vintage%20cars",
      ],
    },
    {
      category: "General%20Knowledge",
      type: "multiple",
      difficulty: "easy",
      question:
        "Which%20of%20these%20colours%20is%20NOT%20featured%20in%20the%20logo%20for%20Google%3F",
      correct_answer: "Pink",
      incorrect_answers: ["Yellow", "Blue", "Green"],
    },
    {
      category: "General%20Knowledge",
      type: "multiple",
      difficulty: "easy",
      question: "Five%20dollars%20is%20worth%20how%20many%20nickles%3F",
      correct_answer: "100",
      incorrect_answers: ["50", "25", "69"],
    },
    {
      category: "General%20Knowledge",
      type: "multiple",
      difficulty: "easy",
      question:
        "What%20do%20the%20letters%20in%20the%20GMT%20time%20zone%20stand%20for%3F",
      correct_answer: "Greenwich%20Mean%20Time",
      incorrect_answers: [
        "Global%20Meridian%20Time",
        "General%20Median%20Time",
        "Glasgow%20Man%20Time",
      ],
    },
    {
      category: "General%20Knowledge",
      type: "multiple",
      difficulty: "easy",
      question:
        "Which%20one%20of%20these%20is%20not%20a%20typical%20European%20sword%20design%3F",
      correct_answer: "Scimitar",
      incorrect_answers: ["Falchion", "Ulfberht", "Flamberge"],
    },
    {
      category: "General%20Knowledge",
      type: "multiple",
      difficulty: "easy",
      question:
        "Which%20American-owned%20brewery%20led%20the%20country%20in%20sales%20by%20volume%20in%202015%3F",
      correct_answer: "D.%20G.%20Yuengling%20and%20Son%2C%20Inc",
      incorrect_answers: [
        "Anheuser%20Busch",
        "Boston%20Beer%20Company",
        "Miller%20Coors",
      ],
    },
    {
      category: "General%20Knowledge",
      type: "multiple",
      difficulty: "easy",
      question:
        "The%20New%20York%20Times%20slogan%20is%2C%20%E2%80%9CAll%20the%20News%20That%E2%80%99s%20Fit%20to%E2%80%A6%E2%80%9D",
      correct_answer: "Print",
      incorrect_answers: ["Digest", "Look", "Read"],
    },
    {
      category: "General%20Knowledge",
      type: "multiple",
      difficulty: "easy",
      question: "Which%20restaurant%27s%20mascot%20is%20a%20clown%3F",
      correct_answer: "McDonald%27s",
      incorrect_answers: ["Whataburger", "Burger%20King", "Sonic"],
    },
    {
      category: "General%20Knowledge",
      type: "multiple",
      difficulty: "easy",
      question:
        "What%20was%20the%20first%20ever%20London%20Underground%20line%20to%20be%20built%3F",
      correct_answer: "Metropolitan%20Line",
      incorrect_answers: [
        "Circle%20Line",
        "Bakerloo%20Line",
        "Victoria%20Line",
      ],
    },
    {
      category: "General%20Knowledge",
      type: "multiple",
      difficulty: "easy",
      question: "How%20tall%20is%20the%20Burj%20Khalifa%3F",
      correct_answer: "2%2C722%20ft",
      incorrect_answers: ["2%2C717%20ft", "2%2C546%20ft", "3%2C024%20ft"],
    },
    {
      category: "General%20Knowledge",
      type: "multiple",
      difficulty: "easy",
      question:
        "Which%20of%20the%20following%20card%20games%20revolves%20around%20numbers%20and%20basic%20math%3F",
      correct_answer: "Uno",
      incorrect_answers: ["Go%20Fish", "Twister", "Munchkin"],
    },
    {
      category: "General%20Knowledge",
      type: "multiple",
      difficulty: "easy",
      question:
        "What%20machine%20element%20is%20located%20in%20the%20center%20of%20fidget%20spinners%3F",
      correct_answer: "Bearings",
      incorrect_answers: ["Axles", "Gears", "Belts"],
    },
    {
      category: "General%20Knowledge",
      type: "multiple",
      difficulty: "easy",
      question: "What%20is%20Tasmania%3F",
      correct_answer: "An%20Australian%20State",
      incorrect_answers: [
        "A%20flavor%20of%20Ben%20and%20Jerry%27s%20ice-cream",
        "A%20Psychological%20Disorder",
        "The%20Name%20of%20a%20Warner%20Brothers%20Cartoon%20Character",
      ],
    },
    {
      category: "General%20Knowledge",
      type: "multiple",
      difficulty: "easy",
      question:
        "What%20company%20developed%20the%20vocaloid%20Hatsune%20Miku%3F",
      correct_answer: "Crypton%20Future%20Media",
      incorrect_answers: ["Sega", "Sony", "Yamaha%20Corporation"],
    },
    {
      category: "General%20Knowledge",
      type: "multiple",
      difficulty: "easy",
      question:
        "In%20which%20fast%20food%20chain%20can%20you%20order%20a%20Jamocha%20Shake%3F",
      correct_answer: "Arby%27s",
      incorrect_answers: ["McDonald%27s", "Burger%20King", "Wendy%27s"],
    },
    {
      category: "General%20Knowledge",
      type: "multiple",
      difficulty: "easy",
      question:
        "What%20zodiac%20sign%20is%20represented%20by%20a%20pair%20of%20scales%3F",
      correct_answer: "Libra",
      incorrect_answers: ["Aries", "Capricorn", "Sagittarius"],
    },
    {
      category: "General%20Knowledge",
      type: "multiple",
      difficulty: "easy",
      question:
        "The%20likeness%20of%20which%20president%20is%20featured%20on%20the%20rare%20%242%20bill%20of%20USA%20currency%3F",
      correct_answer: "Thomas%20Jefferson",
      incorrect_answers: [
        "Martin%20Van%20Buren",
        "Ulysses%20Grant",
        "John%20Quincy%20Adams",
      ],
    },
    {
      category: "General%20Knowledge",
      type: "multiple",
      difficulty: "easy",
      question: "What%20is%20Cynophobia%20the%20fear%20of%3F",
      correct_answer: "Dogs",
      incorrect_answers: ["Birds", "Flying", "Germs"],
    },
    {
      category: "General%20Knowledge",
      type: "multiple",
      difficulty: "easy",
      question:
        "Terry%20Gilliam%20was%20an%20animator%20that%20worked%20with%20which%20British%20comedy%20group%3F",
      correct_answer: "Monty%20Python",
      incorrect_answers: [
        "The%20Goodies%E2%80%8E",
        "The%20League%20of%20Gentlemen%E2%80%8E",
        "The%20Penny%20Dreadfuls",
      ],
    },
    {
      category: "General%20Knowledge",
      type: "multiple",
      difficulty: "easy",
      question:
        "If%20you%20are%20caught%20%22Goldbricking%22%2C%20what%20are%20you%20doing%20wrong%3F",
      correct_answer: "Slacking",
      incorrect_answers: ["Smoking", "Stealing", "Cheating"],
    },
    {
      category: "General%20Knowledge",
      type: "multiple",
      difficulty: "easy",
      question:
        "The%20Flag%20of%20the%20European%20Union%20has%20how%20many%20stars%20on%20it%3F",
      correct_answer: "12",
      incorrect_answers: ["10", "14", "16"],
    },
    {
      category: "General%20Knowledge",
      type: "multiple",
      difficulty: "easy",
      question: "How%20many%20furlongs%20are%20there%20in%20a%20mile%3F",
      correct_answer: "Eight",
      incorrect_answers: ["Two", "Four", "Six"],
    },
    {
      category: "General%20Knowledge",
      type: "multiple",
      difficulty: "easy",
      question:
        "When%20one%20is%20%22envious%22%2C%20they%20are%20said%20to%20be%20what%20color%3F",
      correct_answer: "Green",
      incorrect_answers: ["Red", "Blue", "Yellow"],
    },
    {
      category: "General%20Knowledge",
      type: "multiple",
      difficulty: "easy",
      question:
        "When%20someone%20is%20cowardly%2C%20they%20are%20said%20to%20have%20what%20color%20belly%3F",
      correct_answer: "Yellow",
      incorrect_answers: ["Green", "Red", "Blue"],
    },
    {
      category: "General%20Knowledge",
      type: "multiple",
      difficulty: "easy",
      question:
        "The%20Canadian%20%241%20coin%20is%20colloquially%20known%20as%20a%20what%3F",
      correct_answer: "Loonie",
      incorrect_answers: ["Boolie", "Foolie", "Moodie"],
    },
    {
      category: "General%20Knowledge",
      type: "multiple",
      difficulty: "easy",
      question:
        "Which%20of%20the%20following%20is%20not%20an%20Ivy%20League%20University%3F",
      correct_answer: "Stanford",
      incorrect_answers: [
        "University%20of%20Pennsylvania",
        "Harvard",
        "Princeton",
      ],
    },
    {
      category: "General%20Knowledge",
      type: "multiple",
      difficulty: "easy",
      question:
        "The%20drug%20cartel%20run%20by%20Pablo%20Escobar%20originated%20in%20which%20South%20American%20city%3F",
      correct_answer: "Medell%C3%ADn",
      incorrect_answers: ["Bogot%C3%A1", "Quito", "Cali"],
    },
    {
      category: "General%20Knowledge",
      type: "multiple",
      difficulty: "easy",
      question:
        "Which%20of%20the%20following%20blood%20component%20forms%20a%20plug%20at%20the%20site%20of%20injuries%3F",
      correct_answer: "Platelets",
      incorrect_answers: [
        "Red%20blood%20cells",
        "White%20blood%20cells",
        "Blood%20plasma",
      ],
    },
    {
      category: "General%20Knowledge",
      type: "multiple",
      difficulty: "easy",
      question: "What%20is%20the%20French%20word%20for%20%22fish%22%3F",
      correct_answer: "poisson",
      incorrect_answers: ["fiche", "escargot", "mer"],
    },
    {
      category: "General%20Knowledge",
      type: "multiple",
      difficulty: "easy",
      question:
        "What%20is%20the%20profession%20of%20Elon%20Musk%27s%20mom%2C%20Maye%20Musk%3F",
      correct_answer: "Model",
      incorrect_answers: ["Professor", "Biologist", "Musician"],
    },
    {
      category: "General%20Knowledge",
      type: "multiple",
      difficulty: "easy",
      question: "What%20is%20the%20famous%20Papa%20John%27s%20last%20name%3F",
      correct_answer: "Schnatter",
      incorrect_answers: ["Chowder", "Williams", "ANDERSON"],
    },
    {
      category: "General%20Knowledge",
      type: "multiple",
      difficulty: "easy",
      question:
        "Which%20country%20has%20the%20union%20jack%20in%20its%20flag%3F",
      correct_answer: "New%20Zealand",
      incorrect_answers: ["South%20Africa", "Canada", "Hong%20Kong"],
    },
    {
      category: "General%20Knowledge",
      type: "multiple",
      difficulty: "easy",
      question: "When%20was%20the%20Playstation%203%20released%3F",
      correct_answer: "November%2011%2C%202006",
      incorrect_answers: [
        "January%208%2C%202007",
        "December%2025%2C%202007",
        "July%2016%2C%202006",
      ],
    },
    {
      category: "General%20Knowledge",
      type: "multiple",
      difficulty: "easy",
      question:
        "What%20airline%20was%20the%20owner%20of%20the%20plane%20that%20crashed%20off%20the%20coast%20of%20Nova%20Scotia%20in%201998%3F",
      correct_answer: "Swiss%20Air",
      incorrect_answers: ["Air%20France", "British%20Airways", "TWA"],
    },
  ];
